<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Benjamin Weis</title>
    <link>http://www.benweis.me/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Benjamin Weis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 14:17:08 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.benweis.me/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming the Sum Square Problem</title>
      <link>http://www.benweis.me/blog/programming-the-sum-square-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 14:17:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.benweis.me/blog/programming-the-sum-square-problem/</guid>
      <description>I recently watched an interesting video on the Numberphile YouTube channel where Matt Parker discuses the &amp;lsquo;Sum Square Problem&amp;rsquo;. The video can be seen below.
  The video mentions that the problem is only solved for where n is less than ~300. Over the next week I will be attempting to solve this problem for a larger n than anyone has ever solved before!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making sqlplus Usable</title>
      <link>http://www.benweis.me/blog/making-sqlplus-usable/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.benweis.me/blog/making-sqlplus-usable/</guid>
      <description>I have been taking CS 348: Information Systems this semester and found that using sqlplus on the lab machines is borderline maddening.
A friend helped me configure the rlwrap wrapper utility to make sqlplus less frustrating to use. I wanted to document the process for anyone else who wants sane keyboard editing inside sqlplus.
The Problem with sqlplus Out of the box, sqlplus is quite frustrating to use because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have line editor functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect to Purdue CS files using SSHFS</title>
      <link>http://www.benweis.me/blog/connect-to-purdue-cs-files-using-sshfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.benweis.me/blog/connect-to-purdue-cs-files-using-sshfs/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a quick tutorial on how I access my Purdue CS files remotely so that I can still use all my preferred local development tools, like Sublime Text and my shell customizations.
Install Required Software on Mac OS X I assume you already have Brew and Homebrew Cask installed on your Mac.
 Use cask to install osxfuse:
brew cask install osxfuse Use homebrew to install sshfs:
brew install sshfs  Mount Your Remote Directory  Run the following command to mount the directory to your local machine:  sshfs &amp;lt;username&amp;gt;@data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>